* 欢乐满人间 *
* joy to the world *
* 上帝临大地 *
* the lord has come *
* 世人迎来他们的君主 *
* let earth receive her king *
* 每颗心灵将为他敞开 *
* let every heart prepare him room *
* 天堂尘世皆欢欣歌唱 *
* and heaven and nature sing *
- * 天堂尘世皆欢欣歌唱 *abc- 烂透了
* and heaven,heaven andabcnature sing * this sucks.
所以我们必须说出来
This is why we need toabcmake a statement. You know?
我想这不--
I don'tabcthink that--
怎么了? 你怕被留堂
what?You afraidabcwe'll end up in detention?
是的 老师一定会这么做
Well, yeah, that's--that'sabcwhat teachers do.
不可能罚我们都留堂
They're not going toabcsend all of us to detention.
Henderson先生是个笨蛋abc我们要让他反省一下
Mr. Henderson is totally lame,and this isabcour best chance to inform him of that fact.
你不觉得他很废?
You don't think he's lame?
是 但是--
Well...Yeah,abcbut--
那还有什么问题?
then what's the problem?
好吧
Okay.
有请卡姆登郡爵士合唱团
the camden hills local jazz ensemble.
* 栗子在火中毕剥 *
* Chestnuts roasting on an open fire *
* 小精灵掐你的鼻子 *
* jack frost nipping at your nose *
* 唱诗班唱起圣诞颂歌 *
* yuletide carols being sung by a choir *
* 人们打扮成爱斯基摩人 *
* and folks dressed up like eskimos *
* 人尽皆知Henderson先生是大笨-- *
* everybody knows Mr.Henderson's a stupid-- *
她居然上当了
I can't believe she fell for that.
为-为什么要这样?
Why--why'd you do that?
我--我有点不--舒服
I--I don't feelabcso g-- so good.
16岁女生 被同学作弄abc产生幻觉并呕吐
16-year-old female gets pranked, alsoabcgets visual hallucinations and vomiting.
经检查是肝脏衰竭
Turns out to be a failing liver.
为什么Foreman的胸部abc好端端会忽然下垂?
Why have foreman's breastsabcsuddenly started to droop?
大胸症是你想出来让abcForeman休假的借口
Large breasts are a classic symptom ofabcyou letting foreman take vacation days
他就可以赶在年底前完成给FDA的报告了abc(美国食品与药物管理局)
so he can finish his F.D.A.abcReports before the end of the year.
你什么时候休假?
When are you taking vacation?
涉及肝脏和神经--
hepatic and neurologicalabcinvolvement--
Foreman休假 我可以理解
so I understand foreman's absence.
你不休假 我就不懂了
Your presence, not so much.
我在向你们转介病例abc想必你已经觉察到我的存在了
I'm bringing in a case. You mayabchave noticed me doing that before.
最近想不觉察你都很难
I've noticed you a lot recently.
你频频出现 以至我以为abc你看上了这里的某个人--
It's almost as if you have aabcsexual interest in someone here--
譬如说...Taub
like, say... taub.
鉴于久留此地 会引起Taub误会abc所以我决定走人
Well, taub might think I like him if Iabcstayed, which is why I'm gonna do this.
这和我没什么关系吧
somehow I don't thinkabcthat was really about me.
- 威尔森氏症?abc- 血浆铜蓝蛋白正常
- uh, wilson's disease.abc- ceruloplasmin's normal.
你有一份圣诞礼物
You've got a christmas present.
"Greg--这本书让我想到你"
"Greg--made meabcthink of you."
有意思 这么做后通常会爆炸
That's funny. Usuallyabcexplodes after I do that.
酗酒?
Alcohol abuse?
她才16岁
She's 16.
要是她喝得多到肝脏衰竭abc父母和老师一定会发现
The kind of boozing that destroys your liverabcthat early, parents or teachers would notice.
Joseph Bell的"外科手术指南"
Wow, manual of the operationsabcof surgery by joseph bell.
- 这你也要扔?abc- 再扔一次
- You're throwing that away?abc- Twice.
有人恶作剧 别管它
someone's screwing with me. Forget it.
赠古医书为礼
yeah, gifting antique medical texts.
经典作弄人的桥段
Oldest gag in the book.
字迹像是女孩子的abc你有粉丝了 House?
Handwriting's kinda girly.abcYou got an admirer, house?
我说了别管那书!
I said forget the book!
为什么选中她?
Why'd they pick on her?
她是模范生 成绩好 当志愿者 招人忌恨
She's an overachiever. High grades.abcShe volunteers. She's a big target.
要我说的话
I'm assuming literally.
没准这学校有一群"希德姐妹帮"abc(描写叛逆高中生的电影)
Depending on where this schoolabcfalls on the heathers scale.
你觉得是其他孩子给她下药了?
Do you think the kidsabcslipped her something?
老师已经问过了
Their teachers grilled them.
你什么时候见过学生向老师坦白了?
When do teachers ever knowabchow to motivate their students?
你对Natalie做过什么?
what did you do to natalie?
都怪我
It's all my fault.
没拦着她变人头猪脑
I didn't stop herabcfrom being a total pig.
- 你想干-abc- 你们的朋友肝脏衰竭了
- What are you-- - yourabcfriend's liver is failing.
我们正在尽力抢救abc她可能需要肝脏移植
We're doing what we can, but sheabcstill might need a transplant.
可能会死abc除非你们说出让她吃了什么
She could die unless youabctell us what you gave her.
- 告诉他吧abc- 闭嘴
- Just tell him.abc- Shut up.
我们给她吃了迷幻蘑菇
We gave her some 'shrooms.
我们自己也吃了一点abc我们只是--想让她放松一下
We took some ourselves, we just--abcwanted to make her loosen up a little.
你们可真体贴 还有剩么?
How thoughtful of you. You got any left?
在Simon的储物柜里
They're in simon's locker.
- 是你的主意?abc- 才不是
- This was your idea?abc- No way.
我什么也没干
I didn't give her anything.
没错 你只是袖手旁观abc任由他们为所欲为
Right, you just knew aboutabcit and let them do it.
毒蘑菇和迷幻蘑菇是不一样的
poisonous mushrooms andabchallucinogenic ones are different.
如果烘干方法不对就难说了
Not if they don't dry correctly.
回学校去吧 祈祷我们能把她救回来
get back to school. You betterabchope we got to her in time.
怎么了?
What?
我会有麻烦吗?abc我们是不是应该向她道歉?
Am I going to get in trouble?abcShould we apologize or something?
应该
Yes, you should.
Natalie在三楼病房
Natalie's on the third floor.
- 下面的是谁?abc- 别的病人
- Who's down there?abc- ********
我上周和她说话那个女人呢?
Where's the woman I spoke to last week?
那个参加实验的病人abc出现晚期症状的
The trial patient, um,abcwith the advanced symptoms.
她退出了
She dropped out.
她没事吧?
Is she okay?
与病情无关 是她的个人意愿
Not health-related. Sheabcjust wants to drop out.
为什么?
Why?
她没说
She didn't say.
只有极个别病人能享受我破门而入abc对他们深入了解的待遇
And I only break into the houses of veryabcspecial patients to understand them better.
我状态不错吧 老板?
I do good today, boss?
没有僵硬 没有强直
No rigidity, no cog wheeling.
所以 的确不错
So, absolutely I'd call that good.
好极了 谢谢
Great. Thanks.
- 你的病历夹abc- 放你那了
- Your clipboard.abc- Keep it.
谢谢你帮我
Thanks for helping me out
这地方弥漫着邪恶的味道
this place actually smls of evil.
你工作的地方不也一样?
where do you work, again?
为什么House要把一本abc价值几百刀的书扔掉?
Why would house throw out aabcbook worth hundreds of dollars?
就是为了让你问这个问题
To make you ask that question.
为了耍人 他才不计较花多少钱?
Can you really put a priceabctag on screwing with people?
能帮我们开Natalie Soellner的储物柜么?
Can you get us into natalieabcsoellner's locker while we're here?
House做事有目的性abc不至于为了耍我们-
House always has an agenda.Justabcscrewing with us isn't--
那是 他绝不会这么做abc慢-- 他去年做过了
yeah, he'd never do that. Oh,abcwait-- he already did last year.
记得 他去年给自己abc送了一份神秘圣诞礼物么?
Remember the secretabcsanta gift he got himself?
上次是为了让我们窝里斗abc争相给他送礼
He was making us fight over whoabccould get him the best present.
这次只是引起我们好奇
This time he's just making us wonder.
没有挑拨离间 没有挑起竞争
No animosity, no ugly competition.
也许真是别人送他的
I think it's a real present.
如果是真的abc那House就真吓了一跳
If it's real, thenabchouse really was freaked.
如果他的情绪受到影响abc到头来遭殃的还是我们
And if it affects him,abceventually it'll affect us.
也许给Natalie下毒的不是别人
Maybe it wasn't thoseabckids who poisoned natalie.
而是Natalie自己
Maybe it was natalie herself.
我不是想自杀
I didn't try to kill myself.
那你藏着这么多止痛片干吗?
Then why'd you haveabcall those painkillers?
以防哪天头痛
In case I get a headache.
也许你吃的有点多了
Well, maybe you took a few too many.
你有孩子吗?
Do you have any kids?
没有
No.
但我高中时和你没什么两样
But high school wasn't all thatabcdifferent when I was your age.
十几岁孩子有时坏得很abc我完全能了解你的遭遇
Teenagers can be incredibly mean.abcI know what you're going through.
你当时一定很得意吧
I bet you were cool.
你这么漂亮
You're pretty.
你也很漂亮
You're pretty, too.
我很胖 我是失败者
I'm fat. I'm a loser.
大家都讨厌我
They all hate me.
知道他们去年怎么对我吗?
You know what they did last year?
他们给我拍照 说是学校编年鉴用...
They took these photosabcof me for the yearbook...
他们骗人 他们把照片传到网上
but it wasn'T. It was for this website.
拿我开玩笑...说我是猪
Making fun of me... calling me a pig.
别管他们
Forget about them.
- 先把你的病治好abc- 有什么意义呢?
- Let's just make you better.abc- What's the point?
乙酰半胱氨酸可以保住她的肝脏
Acetylcysteine could save her liver.
但如果她真吃了那些药
But we have to act fast.
我们就得尽快采取其它治疗--
If there's any chanceabcthat she took all those pills--
绝不可能
there's no chance.
好吧
Okay.
她原本是个快乐 可爱的小女生abc但自从一年前进入了青春期
She was the happiest,sweetest littleabcgirl and-- and a year ago she hits puberty,
仿佛在她的身体里abc住进了一个陌生人
and it's like this secretiveabclittle stranger moved into her room.
我试着和她沟通
I try to talk to herabcabout what s's going through.
给她治疗吧
Give her the treatment.
- 难道你认为她--abc- 我不知该怎么办了
- You can't really think that sheabctried-- - I don't know what to think.
如果是法庭传票abc这样的礼物他以前也收到过
If it's a subpoena, he's gottenabcthat kind of present before.
是一本书
It was a book.
这就缩小了范围
That narrows it down.
把目标定在那些识字而且abc到过书店的人身上就行了
Just look for someone who knows howabcto reador has been to a bookstore.
但很少有书店卖Joseph Bell的手术指南
Most bookstores don'tabccarry joseph bell on surgery.
有留言么?
Did it have a note?
"Greg-- 这本书让我想到你"
"Greg--madeabcme think of you."
包装纸是绿色的?
Green wrapping paper?
你怎么知道?
How did you know that?
你想到了?
What is it?
没什么
It's nothing.
是么--既然没有
Yes--whenabcsomething'snothing,
为什么你能猜到包装纸的颜色
the natural response is to guessabcthe color of the paper it's wrapped in
尔后又陷入了深深的沉默?
and then descend into stunned silence?
Irene Adler 2001年圣诞节
Irene adler. Christmas, 2001.
出现肉状瘤的症状abc甲氨蝶呤对她无效
Sarcoid symptoms, but sheabcdidn't respond to methotrexate.
我从未见他如此心焦
I've never seen him so obsessed.
最后关头他做出了韦格纳病的诊断abc救了她命 这么长时间相处--
He saved her with a last minute wegener'sabcdiagnosis, but the hours he put in--
我以为会使他痛苦
I thought it would kill him.
然而...
And then...
他爱上了她
well, he fell for her.
但当时Stacy才离开他不久--
But it was too soonabcafter stacy and--
意想不到的是 Irene先放手了
It sounds silly, but ireneabcwas the one who got away.
真的?
Really?
不 你们两个白痴 House在耍你们呢
No, you idiots. Houseabcis just screwing with you.
你们真以为有某个神秘女人abc会用绿色包装纸作为标记?
You think there's some woman with aabcmysterious green wrapping paper trademark?
那你怎么猜到--
Then how did you guess--
我乱猜的
I could be wrong.
也有可能是某个倾慕者送了House一本书abc恰好和我去年送的一样
It's possiblea secret admirer gave houseabcthe same book I gave him last christmas.
而且恰好用了同款包装纸abc并写了同样内容的纸条
And the same paper I wrappedabcit in and the note I wrote.
有状况
We got go.
- 心跳多少?
heartbeat?
150 血压180/110 不能再往上升了
Crackling 3/4 of the way up.
也就是说 她没有想自杀
Guess this means sheabcdidn't try to kill herself.
把幻觉一项划掉 是蘑菇引起的
Well, scratch the hallucinations.abcThat's from the mushrooms.
留下肝脏衰竭和肺水肿
Leaves liver failure andabcnow pulmonary edema.
还有你-- 站在那一脸哀怨
And you-- standingabcthere,beseechingly.
没错 我本来要去你家盯梢abc不巧这周很忙 而你办公室比较近
Yes, I was goingto stalk you at home, butabcit was a busy week and your office is closer.
13和Foreman忙着做药物实验
thirteen and foremanabcwere busy drug trialing
我们需要药物过量的会诊abc所以把她找来了
and we needed an answer on theabcoverdose, so we called her in.
她只是为我们提供建议
She's just updating us.
- 这倒方便abc- 建议完毕
- Convenient.abc- Update's done.
小时我爸妈从没闹过离婚abc你们的斗法让我大开眼界
This is a good experience for me,abcas my parents never got divorced.
- 继续发言abc- 嗅胶(以达麻醉 迷幻效果)
- Theories?abc- Glue sniffing.
其作用会即时在肺部反映
effects on the lungs wouldabchave been immediate.
House 我们知道怎么回事了
house, we all know what's going on here.
- 礼物是Cuddy送的abc- 不是
- Cuddy gave you that present.abc- No.
感染?
Infections?
没有发热 唾液里没有多形核白细胞
No fever, no polys in the sputum.
我觉得-她喜欢你
I think-- I thinkabcshe loves you.
都叫你别管礼物了
I told you to lay off the present.
迷幻药也别管了
And the L.S.D.
不要被止痛药扰乱了视线
We got distracted by the painkillers.
最大可能性还是中毒--
Toxins are still theabcmost likely--
把你的感受告诉她
just tell her how you feel.
如果你不说 我去说
If you won't,then I will.
我替你跟她直说了 管它呢
I'll walk right down there. Damn it.
爱不应受到束缚
Love like this needs to fly free.
你们找过Wilson了
You talked to wilson.
顺便说句abc他的字迹很女孩子气
He has veryabcgirly handwriting, by the way.
早知就把礼物重新包装一遍
I knew I should have justabcwrapped a new present.
你说病人做过志愿者 在哪里?
you said the patient volunteered. Where?
快乐谷
Uh, pleasant valley.
特伦顿的施食处
Soup kitchen in trenton.
13还有Kutner 去搜病人的住处和学校abcTaub...
Thirteen and kutner,search theabchome and the school. taub...
Taub给病人照顾过的流浪汉做肛门拭子
you take the anal swabbing of theabcfragrant and contagious homeless man.
你为什么不去影碟店 逢人就说凯文斯派西abc是Keyser Soze?(悬疑电影"非常嫌疑犯")
why don't you hang out in the video storeabcand tell everyone kevin spacey's keyser soze?
顺便说一句 这电影的结尾没劲透了
And by the way, that endingabcreally made no sense at all.
你收了我礼物一年都没拆?
You had my present for aabcyear and didn't even open it?
我怎知里头是一本超贵古董书
I had no way of knowing thereabcwas an expensive book inside.
即便以你的标准而言abc这玩笑也开得太无聊了
Completely meaninglessabcprank, even for you.
偷你的雪糕才无聊abc虽然分外好吃
Stealing your ice cream is aabccompletely meaningless, albeit delicious,prank.
观察手下对反常现象的反应abc则有助于我的工作
Observing my team's reactions toabcunexplained phenomena could have been pretty useful.
捉弄别人的法子这么多abc为什么偏偏给自己送礼物?
Of all the ways to mess with people,abcwhy give yourself an imaginary present?
你最近调查过消防员脱衣舞男的行情么?
Have you checked the pricesabcfor fireman strippers recently?
对了 圣诞假期对你来说煞是难熬
Yes. The holidays-- they'reabchard for you. I get it.
眼看着周围的人互赠礼物
You see the people around youabcgiving and receiving gifts,
并维持着恒久而真挚的恋情abc但你却无法办到
having sustained,meaningfulabcrelationships, and since you can't,
潜意识作用下abc便给自己送了一份礼物
someing deepin your subconscious makesabcyou create the appearance of a gift.
可怜
Sad.
你这水准也能通过精神科实习?
You really passed your psych rotation?
可惜你无法对人友善
It's too bad you can't justabcbe nice to people.
因此也无法得到真正的礼物
You could get a real present that way.
如果我想要礼物 我只要凝视病人abc然后摆出你那副
If I wanted gifts, I would just lookabcdeep into my patients' eyes and act like you.
"噢 我很遗憾你快死了 蠢驴太太"
"Oh, I'm so sorry you'reabcdying, "mrs. Moron.
"跟你上床当然没问题"
"Of course I'll sleep with you.
"虽然我技巧不佳 但-"
What I lack in skill Iabccan make up for in--"
你还是直接开涮得了abc叫她蠢驴太太什么的
you'd just wind up insultingabcher, perhaps calling her Mrs. Mor.
没错 因为我生来就不懂礼貌为何物
Right, 'cause I'm physicallyabcincapable of being polite.
指望你长久保持诚恳和友善?
Being kind in aabcsustained,meaningful way?
没门
No.
噢 我懂了
Oh, I get it.
你想逼我反其道而行
You're trying to getabcme to prove you wrong,
那么在圣诞节期间abc我就会对病人大发善心
then I'm gonna be nice to all myabcpatients all through the holiday season,
Potter先生也不会偷吃小Tim的麦片粥了abc真让人感动 (圣诞电影"风云人物")
and then mr. Potter won't steal tinyabctim's porridge. I'm totally on it.
没错 我是这么打算来着
Yeah, that actually isabcwhat I'm trying to do.
可悲的是 对你没效果
And the pathetic partabcis, it's not gonna work.
你说得对
You're right.
我不能老是当混蛋
I gotta stop being such a jerk.
我要洗心革面去了
Oops. Just kindabcof undercut myself, there.
Janice? 我是Remy 我-
Janice? I'm remy.I'm--
我记得你
yeah, I remember you.
- 听说你退出了试验abc- 是的
- I heard you left the trial.abc- Yeah.
有我能帮忙的--
If there's some way I could help--
是那个医生
um, it-- itabcwas that doctor.
他是做试验的医生
He--the one that wasabcrunnin' the tests.
-Foreman医生abc-是的
- Dr. Foreman.abc- Yeah.
他是很出色的神经科医生 他是个好人
He's a great neurologist.abcHe's a great guy.
你喜欢他?
You--youabclike him?
你不喜欢么?
Why don't you?
我跟他说过 注射让我泛恶心
I told him that those injections wereabcmaking me sick in my stomach,
但他只给了我抗酸剂
and he just gave me antacid.
提醒过会有反胃的副作用abc他也只能给你抗酸剂
We were warned that nausea's a side effect, andabcgiving you antacids is all he really could do.
他没有 他跟我说"挺过去"
No, he told me, "get over it."
用不用药 我都活不长了
With or without the use ofabcdrugs, I don't have a long time.
我不想剩下的时间做他的小白鼠
I'm not gonna endabcit be in' his guinea pig.
House
house.
是肺结核
It's tuberculosis.
你从肛门试样看出来的? 你可真厉害
You got that from an analabcswab? Man, you're good.
还有另外一个线索
There was a more subtle clue.
流浪汉 咳血
Homeless guy,abcuncontrollably hacking up blood.
咳嗽了两个星期 他病得不轻
Cough's lasted twoabcmonths,he was cachectic.
除非你能把他和病人联系起来
Unless you can tieabchim to the patient--
我再说一遍 还有些细小的线索
yes, again, if only thereabcwas some subtle clue,
比如在她一整周给人打饭时 他都站在旁边
like the fact that he was standingabcnext to her in the soup line for a week.
我讨厌这么有勇气的人
I hate spunk.
肺结核可以引发肝脏衰竭和肺部症状abc符合
T.B. Can cause liverabcfailure, lung symptoms--fits.
给她用标准疗法治
Start her on the standard regimen.
你今天不用去门诊
Uh--you don'tabchave clinic duty today.
我可不把它当义务
Who says it's a duty?
我是Greg
I'm greg.
你好 我是Whitney
Hi, I'm whitney.
你好 Whitney 我能帮你什么嘛?
Hi, whitney. How can I help you?
我头疼得很
I have a-- aabcterrible headache.
哦 这可不好
Oh, sorry to hear that.
我给你治治
I'll get you fixed up.
你还需要什么? 喝杯水 咖啡 薄荷茶?
Is there anything else you need?abcBottle of water? Coffee? Mint tea?
不用了 但是谢谢你
No, but that's so nice.
通常门诊医生都很着急的
Usually the clinicabcdoctors are kind of rushed.
如果你不够友善 怎么能当医生呢
If you can't be nice, why be a doctor?
你那里感到疼?
So where do you feel the pain?
我头的后面
In the back of my head here.
这是贝卡里亚氏记号
That's beccaria's sign.
第三个月就会消失 (双关"第三学期")
That'll be gone by your third trimester.
我没在上学
Oh, I'm not in school.
你的胎儿也没上学
Neither is your fetus.
天啊
Oh, god.
你不知道你怀孕了?
You didn't know you were pregnant?
你怎么能通过头疼就知道呢?
How do--you know that justabcfrom the headache?
我怎么知道的?
How do I know?
我月经没来 我变胖了 呕吐
I missed my period, I got fat,threw up,
- 哦 等下 应该是你察觉abc-什么?
- oh, no, wait--that'sabchow you know. - What?
我知道 是因为你肿胀的胸部abc都快把你的上衣撑破了
I know because of the tight shirtabcstretched over the swollen boobs,
整个门诊都快跟你一样口味变咸
the salt cravingabcyou've imported into the clinic,
防动晕贴片对你的晨吐没有帮助
the motion sickness patch that doesn't do anythingabcfor the kind of sickness that you feel in the morning.
我是个处女 我未婚夫也是
Yeah, I'm a virgin. So is my fianc?
我相信他
I believe him.
还有其他什么方式我能怀孕么?
Aren't there other ways Iabccould get pregnant, like...
坐在马桶圈上?
sitting on a toilet seat?
如果你和马桶圈之间还有个男的坐着的话abc肯定会的
Absolutely--there would need to be a guy sittingabcbetween you and the toilet seat, but yes, absolutely.
我干得可真好
I was doing so well.
Natalie?
-天啊abc-Natalie 她痉挛了
- Oh, god.abc- Natalie. She's having a seizure.
翻过去 护士！
Put her on her side. Nurse!
是因为肺结核么?
Is this from the T.B.?
不会有颈软 我不知道是什么
Not with the supple neck.abcI don't know what this is.
四毫克氯羟安定
Four milligrams lorazepam.
肝 肺 现在是脑
liver, lungs, and now brain...
再次神秘出现
which has mysteriously reappeared.
说到再次神秘出现
Speaking of mysterious lyreappeared.
她的丙氨酸氨基转移酶是正常的20倍
Her A.L.T.Is 20 times normal.
转氨酶和凝血酶原时间太高
Transaminases and P.T.'S way up.
肝脏快不行了
She's gonna lose her liver.
我们得把她加入移植名单上
We gotta get her on the transplant list.
你总是出现
You keep showing up.
然后老是离开
you also keep leaving.
有可能你太想得到我abc却真的很讨厌这个孩子
It's possible that you have the hotsabcfor me, but really really hate this kid.
但是也有极小的可能 我弄反了
It's also remotely possibleabcthat I have that reversed.
她是个不错的孩子 我想让她没事
She's a nice kid. I wannaabcmake sure she's okay.
肝纤维化?
Hepatic fibrosis?
补体水平正常 肝脏大小正常
Normal complementabclevel,normal-sized liver.
她让你想起了...你?
she remind you of... you?
不是 你高中时候可不失败
Nah, you weren't a loser in high school.
那些男孩子因为你梦遗
You had every tom, dick, andabchershel wet-dreaming about you.
但她可能让你想起另一个
But she could be making youabcthink of another helpless,
你最近遇到的胖娃娃
chubby little girl you recently met.
别跟我说你是指我想收养的婴儿
You are not really making thisabcabout the baby I tried to adopt.
已经几个星期了
it's been a few weeks.
够你走出伤感了
Just enough time toabcget over hurt feelings.
Natalie 16岁
Natalie's 16.
我想你把人性和母性混淆了
I think you're confusing beingabcmaternal with being human.
如果我们当初没排除蘑菇
If we hadn'truledabcout the mushrooms--
也许不该排除
maybe we shouldn't have.
别管中毒了 想想过敏的可能
forget toxic--abcthink allergic.
严重的过敏可能引起肝衰竭abc呼吸停止和脑病
Severe mold allergy could cause, uh, liverabcfailure, respiratory arrest, and encephalopathy.
她好几天前吃的蘑菇 不应该还在生病
She ate the 's hrooms days ago.abcThere's no way she'd still be sick.
除非她同时真菌感染
Unless it also gaveabcher a fungal infection.
给她做皮肤点刺 测试抗真菌药
give her a prick test in antifungals.
谢谢你的礼物 我很喜欢
Thank you for the gift.abcI really appreciate it.
我和Janice谈过了
I spoke to janice.
-她还好?abc-是的
- She okay?abc- Yeah.
她感到恶心 她说你让她挺过去?
Her nausea-- she said youabctold her to, like, get over it?
然后呢?
And?
恶心并非靠意志力就能挺过去的
Nausea isn't something you canabcovercome with sheer will power.
我也没开给她意志力的方子
Which is why I didn't prescribe willpower.
给她开了抗酸剂
I prescribed antacids.
如果她挺不过去 早晚会离开试验
If she can't handle that, she'dabchave to leave the trial anyway.
给她打电话 说你很抱歉 她就会回来
Just call her,say you'reabcsorry. She'll come back.
不
No.
你现在很像House
God, you're acting like house now.
我可不像House 所以我也不需要道歉
No, I'm not acting like house, which isabcexactly why I don't need to apologize.
我既不残忍 也不想控制别人
I'm not being cruel. I'mabcnot being manipulative.
我情绪不好的时候abc你跟我说了一模一样的话
You said the same thing to me whenabcI told youI was having a hard time.
确实好用
And it worked.
她是个四十岁的女人abc生理和心理都很糟糕
She's a 40-year-old woman who's fallingabcapart physically and emotionally.
她要死了
She's dying.
我知道 圣诞节死人对你来说不好过
Look, I know seeing the ghostabcof your christmas future is tough.
但是我能帮她的唯一方法是abc让她遵守治疗要求
But the only way I can help her isabcto make sure she follows her regimen,
并非告诉她怎么活
not by becoming her life coach.
你不是像House
You're not acting like house.
你根本就是他
You are like him.
House医生?
Dr. House?
这是我未婚夫 Geoff
This is my fianc? geoff.
她说 你跟她说坐在马桶圈上就可以怀孕
She says you told her you can getabcpregnant from sitting on a toilet seat.
我说了那些词语 但设定了特殊的场景
I said those words, butabcwith a particular inflection.
我知道那不是真的
I knew it was untrue.
还有其他可能性吗 绝无可能么?
Well, is there any otherabcway? Isn't it possible?
报道说有个士兵abc在内战时期睾丸中了一枪
There was a reported case of a civil warabcsoldier who was shot in the testicles,
这个步枪子弹连同睾丸里的"子弹"
and th musket ball carriedabcthe non-musket ball
射到了在附近田野里劳作的女人子宫里
into the uterus of a womanabcworking in a neighboring field.
九个月后 神奇地生下了一个孩子
Nine months later,aabcmiracle child was born.
不过 也许她出轨了
Also, maybe she cheated on you.
我们互相承诺
We made a promise.
我们在床上干其它的事情
We d--we do otherabcstuff in bed.
有没有可能他的精子进入了子宫?
Couldn't some of his spermabchave made it up there somehow?
准确点 精子是通过插入的阴茎来到子宫
More likely,it came from the guy whoseabcpenis made it up there somehow. But...
当然 任何事情都是可能的
sure, anything's possible.
我想做亲子测试
I want a paternity test.
跟他说 在怀孕初期抽取羊水是很危险的
Tell him that amnios are dangerousabcthis early onin the pregnancy.
-是么?abc-谁在乎阿?他不知道
- Are they?abc- Well, who cares? He doesn't know.
我们做亲子鉴定
Well, we'll--we'lldoabcthe paternity test.
没有反应
No reaction.
不好么?
That's bad?
如果是真菌过敏的话 就能解释病状
If you had a mold allergy, itabcwould explain your symptoms.
我们会搞明白的 别担心
We'll find out what's wrong,don't worry.
我知道有些事情abc父母在身边的话不方便说
And, uh,I know some things are hardabcto talk about with your parents around,
但是同学确实恶劣
but kids can be really mean.
有一些人你可以倾诉 或是心理辅导
There are people you can talk to-- programs--
我会没事的
I'll--I'llabcbe okay.
你精神很好 你感觉好点了?
You're in good spirits.abcYou feeling better?
我只是做作业
No. I was just doing my homework.
我是个书呆子 我想这会让我高兴点
I'm such a dork, Iabcguess that cheers me up.
-你爸妈拿来的?abc-不是 Simon拿来的
- Parents brought it?abc- ******
你班上的那个孩子?
The jocky kid in your class?
嗯 他刚走
Yeah. He just left.
保安
Security.
我只是帮她把作业拿来
I was just bringing her her homework.
你捉弄这个小女孩 并拒绝承担责任
You helped bully this little girl andabccompletely refuse to accept responsibility.
你根本不是出于同情才来的
No way you came here out of compassion.
只是因为内疚 你对她做什么了?
That only leaves guilt.abcWhat'd you do to her?
-什么也没有abc-别撒谎了
- Nothing.abc- Stop lying.
要不我把你更衣室里找到的毒品交给警察abc你这个小混蛋
Or I'll take the drugs I found in your lockerabcdown to the cops,you slimy little jerk.
这孩子没对你做什么
This kid didn't do anything to you.
-这跟我没关系abc-好 好 我知道了
- This isn't about me.abc- Yeah, yeah, yeah. I get it.
你在学校的时候也受欺负 冷静点
You were bullied yourself whenabcyou were in school. Take it easy.
我没有
I wasn't bullied.
对 领养来的印度小孩abc亲生父母在他面前被枪杀
Right--the indian foster kid whoseabcparents were shot in front of him.
你当然是返校舞会皇帝
You were clearly homecoming king.
再试一遍 告诉我
Let's try thisabcagain.Just tell me--
老实说 你不明白
honestly,you don't understand.
我们曾是朋友
We used to be friends.
如果不被人取笑的话abc我现在还会做她的朋友
And I'd be friends with her now if,abcyou know, people wouldn't make fun of me.
能跟我说点有用的么?
There's nothing youabccould tell us that'll help?
她跟你们说过她以前喝很多酒么?
Did she mention she used to drink a lot?
没有 你怎么知道的
no. How do you know that?
别告诉任何人好么
Look, don't tell anyone,all right?
我有我哥哥的身份证 我帮别人买酒
I had my brother's I.D.AndabcI kind of supplied people.
以前我每周都给她弄几瓶伏特加
I used to get her a fewabcbottles of vodka each week.
那为什么不干了?
Why'd you stop?
她搞到了身份证 说自己买会便宜些
She got her own I.D.Said itabcwas cheaper buying it herself.
你可以走了
You can go.
我想诊断有结果了
I think we got our diagnosis.
小姑娘是个酒鬼
Our little girl's a drunk.
我不喝酒了 我原来喝 但是
I don't drink.Iabcdid back then, but--
你会死的
you could die.
不知道你的肝脏为什么衰竭abc不能把你加到移植名单上
We can't get you on the transplant listabcuntil we know why your liver is failing.
酗酒能够解释
Alcohol abuse would explain that.
痉挛可能因戒酒引起
The seizures could be from withdrawal.
我六个月没喝酒了
I haven't drunk in six months.
原来也没有喝很多
I didn't even drink that much back then.
一周好几瓶伏特加?
A couple of vodka bottles a week?
我有一半都没打开
I didn't open half of them.
我买是因为Simon卖这些
I just bought them because-- youabcknow, 'cause simon was selling them.
我们原来是朋友
We used to be friends.
那似乎是唯一能让他和我说话的方法
And that's, like,the only way Iabccould get him to even talk to me.
为什么不继续买了呢abc他说你有了自己的假身份证
Then why did you stop buying fromabchim? He said you got your own I.
-我不知道abc-这不是教人满意的回答
- I don't know.abc- See, that's not a good answer.
记得你过问我有没有小孩么?
Remember when you askedabcme if I had any kids?
我没有 也许和这根本没关系
I don't. I don't know, maybeabcit has nothing to do with it,
我会念书 工作能干 但处理不好生活
but I was good at school,abcgood at work,lousy at life.
我搞砸了每一段感情
I screwed upabcevery relationship I ever had.
我想"干嘛要孩子呢?"
And I thought,"why would iabcwant to bring a child into this?"
然后我年纪增长
But then I got older. And...
你现在的感觉会过去的
how you feel now will pass.
别让它影响你一生
Don't let it screw up your whole life.
已经搞糟了
It's already screwed up.
我的哮喘
My asthma.
他们说能治好 但是没一点改善
They said they'd fix it, but itabcdidn't make any difference at all.
有时候医生会犯错误
Well, sometimes doctors make mistakes...
之后得花两倍的精力去纠正
anna,and then you have toabctry twice as hard to fix them.
你有使用吸入器么?
Are you using your inhaler?
一直 一周用掉一个
All the time. Go through one a week.
确定使用方法正确?
You sure you're using it right?
-  我看起来像笨蛋么?abc-不
- Do I look like an idiot?abc- No.
要不演示一下怎么使用吸入器吧
Why don't you showabcme how your inhaler works?
混蛋
Jerk.
这是怎么了?
Uh, what was that all about?
牙买加鸡肉食谱
Jamaican chicken recipes.
父母不同意使用抗焦虑药abc我还是觉得Natalie没说出真相
The parents said no to the benzos, but Iabcstill think natalie's not being honest with me.
她宁可死也不承认酗酒
So she's willing to die toabccover up some boozing.
她非常沮丧
She's very depressed.
她感觉被其他孩子排挤是她应得的
She feels like she deserves whatabcthe other kids are oushing t on her.
我觉得她要不就真的想死abc要不就是想用死亡引起别人的注意
I think she either wants to die or sheabcwants the attention that dying gives her.
我不知道你为什么这么关心
I have no idea why you care so much.
跟Kutner说 开始给她用抗焦虑药
Tell kutner to start her on benzos.
House 父母刚刚
House, the parents just-
不是酒精中毒 痉挛 完全不一样
Not the alcoholism.abcSeizures. Totally different.
不需要他们的许可
Don't need their approval for that.
确定你们想知道?
You sure you want to know?
如果能做一了结 我就告诉你们
If it makes it any easier,abcI'm gonna tell you anyway.
我们想知道
We want to know.
怎么说的?
What does it say?
别走
Don't leave.
昨晚你回家了吗?
You go home last night?
我本来这么打算的abc但一开始看这份文件就停不下来了
I meant to. Started reading thisabcfile, just couldn't put it down.
问你一下 那个放弃的病人abc我跟你谈过的
Let me ask you-- that patient thatabcdropped out, the one I told you about--
怎么了
yeah.
你觉得我该多劝她一下么?
You think i should pursue it more?
不用 病人会放弃abc所以一开始要挑几百个病人治疗
No, patients drop out. That'sabcwhy we start with hundreds.
我只是想abc如果有一个能让放弃的病人回来的简单方法
Well, I just thought if there's an easy way to makeabcthe people who drop off come back, then why not--
-他们不是人abc-真的?
- they're not people.abc- Really?
我以为僵尸试验第二阶段就完成了
I thought the zombie trials wereabcall completed during phase two.
你不能把他们当人看 甚至不能当成病人
You can't see the patients as people.abcYou can't even see them as patients.
- 他们只是编号abc- 但
- They're numbers.abc- Look...
我的一个朋友有这种疾病
a friend of mine has this disease.
我不想知道
I don't wanna know.
这么想是有原因的abc任何私心杂念都会影响研究
There's a reason this is double-blind--abcany personal stake we have skews the studies.
科学不是人际关系 是结果
Science is not about humanabcrelationships. It's about results.
你该知道的 你为House工作
Now, you know that. You work for house.
你想我为什么会选你当搭档?
Why do you think i broughtabcyou on as my partner?
Taub医生
Dr. Taub!
她在和我说话 然后就昏过去了
She was talking to me andabcthen she just passed out.
她的心跳在下降
Her heart's slowing down.
救救她啊 救救她啊
Can you fix it? Can you fix it?
我在
I'm trying.
注射一单位阿托品
Pushing one amp atropine.
我们等了6个多小时了
we've been waiting here for six hours.
父亲是我吗?
Am I the father or not?
不是 但是...
No. But...
她没有出轨
she also didn't cheat on you.
正常情况下 精卵结合 DNA相遇
Normally, sperm meets egg,abcD. N. A. Meets D. N. A.,
进入子宫 细胞分裂 怀胎九月abc婴儿啼哭降生
Goes back to her place, cells divide,abcnine months later, joy is bundled.
这是正常情况
That's normally.
不正常的话 卵子会出现2个基因变异
Abnormally, an egg could have twoabcnaturally occurring gene mutations
正常情况下不会同时发生
that don't naturally occur together.
自发性钙峰会让卵细胞自体受精
A spontaneous calcium spike coulprepabcthe egg for fertilization without sperm,
细胞分化信号出错abc尽管未发生精卵结合 卵子开始分裂
and a division mistake could let the egg splitabcup without ever needing male D. N. A. At all.
单性生殖 没有父亲的孩子
Parthenogenesis. A baby without a daddy.
在人类身上 这只是理论 从未被证实过
In humans, it's onlyever beenabctheorized, but it was never proved.
直到现在
Until now.
妈妈 孩子
Mommy. Baby.
你的女儿只有母亲DNA
Your daughter has only maternal D. N. A.
我亲自检查了5遍
I personally checked this five times.
7个月后 就会...
In seven months,you will have...
处女生子
a virgin birth.
圣诞快乐
Merry christmas.
门诊的那个病人啊
Gotta tell you about is clinic patient.
Natalie的肝衰竭更严重了abc现在又出现心动过缓
Natalie's liver is continuingabcto fail. And now bradycardia.
阿托品不能维持她的心律
Atropine isn't keeping the heart rate up.
我们得给她装起搏器
We're gonna have to putabcher on a pacemaker.
戒酒会导致心跳过快 不是放缓
Alcohol withdrawal would causeabcher heart to race, not crawl.
她的心脏没有任何结构性问题
There's nothingabcstructurally wrong with her heart.
心电图 超声心动图abc电解质水平都正常
E. K. G., Echo,abcelectrolyte panel are all normal.
多发性内分泌综合症?
Multiple endocrine syndrome?
甲状腺素水平正常 下视丘脑瘤?
Free t-4's normal.abcHypothalamic brain tumor?
CT扫描正常
Didn't come upon the C.T.Scan.
攻击了所有器官了 问题可能出在血液abc碱性磷酸酶水平呢?
It's hitting all her organs. Couldabcbe the blood. What's her alk phos?
- 300
300.
不可能是白血病
It can't be leukemia.
碱性磷酸酶偏高也可能是肝衰竭造成的
High alk phos could alsoabcbe from liver failure.
她才十多岁abc骨骼生长和损坏会影响碱性磷酸酶
She's a teenager--means bone growthabcand destruction could throw it off.
可能 但还是偏高
Maybe, but it's higher than you'd expect.
开始化疗
Start her on chemo.
做个骨髓活检确认
We'll do a bone marrow biopsy to confirm.
你怎么只做化验不治病?
Why are you ordering testsabcinstead of treatment?
她的心脏和肝脏就要停摆了
Her heart and liverabcare about to give up.
有什么办法就用啊
Do whatever you need to.
你为什么这么在乎她?
Why are you so attached to this girl?
你决定吧
It's your call.
他不想我们治疗她
He doesn't want us to treat her.
如果是白血病abc即使清除干净所有癌细胞
If it's leukemia, even ifabcwe kill every cancer cell,
她心脏和肝的受损也太严重了
her heart and liver are too far gone.
- 双重移植...abc- 还牵扯进了大脑?
- A double transplant--abc- with brain involvement?
委员会根本都不会看档案
The committee won't even open the file.
如果不能救命abc干吗要她吃化疗的那些苦呢
There's no reason to put a dying girl through aabcpainful treatment if it can't save her.
他这是好意
He's being kind.
我让他们做活检
I'll arrange a biopsy.
Burke夫人?
Mrs. Burke?
我们同时还在进行另一项试验
We are conducting anotherabctrial in tandem with yours.
一样的药 剂量要低
Same drug, lower dose.
恶心不会那么严重
The nausea will be less.
我查了一下 我可以给你换组
I did some checking. I can switch you.
要是你想回来 把表填下吧
Here's the forms if you want back in.
要是我们错了呢?
What if we're wrong?
也许我们不该排除自体免疫疾病
Maybe we shouldn't haveabcoverlooked autoimmunes.
- 高沉降率...abc- 我们讨论过了
- High sed rate--abc- we went over this.
补体水平正常
Normal complement level.
所以不是肝纤维化
So it isn't hepatic fibrosis.
可能是微血管炎
Could still beabcmicroangiopathic vasculitis.
用高剂量的类固醇 说不定能够...
With high-dose steroids,abcwe might be able to reverse--
你管这家医院 每天治上万人
you run a hospital that treatsabcthousands of patients every day.
有些救不活 天天如此
Some of them die. Every day.
如果对每个人你都这么上心...
If you're gonna get this workedabcup over every one of them--
好的!
yes!
- 马上回来abc- 是什么?
- B. R. B.abc- What is it?
病人送的礼物
Thank you from a patient.
给你的?
For you?
我告诉他们 她怀孕是单性生殖abc从而拯救了他们的婚姻
I saved her marriage by showing that herabcpregnancy was the result of parthenogenesis.
人的单性生殖? 你证明了...
Human parthenogenesis?Youabcproved--
是啊 真难以置信
yep. It's unbelievable.
但我亲自检查了5遍
But I personally checked it five times.
你怎么查了5遍?
How did you check it five times?
扩增仪坏了 你必须送出去abc至少要...
The cycler's broken, you would have hadabcto send it out.It would have taken--
是啊...
oh, yeah.
确实挺不可能的 现在想想
That does sound impossible,abcnow that I think of it.
可能更好的解释是abc亲子鉴定表明她偷情了
I guessthe better explanation is thatabcthe paternity test showed she cheated
所以单性生殖是我自己伪造的
so I faked theabcwhole parthenogenesis thingy.
什么? 为什么?
What? Why?
我赢了
I win.
你编出个科学奇迹abc就为了赢和Wilson打的赌?
You fakeda scientific miracleabcjust to win a bet with wilson?
嗯 更像是个争论
Mmm, more an argument.
我知道直接造假亲子鉴定更容易
I realize it would have been simplerabcto just fake the paternity test,
但是 现在可是圣诞节呐
but hey--christmas spiritabcand all that.
我觉得你又善恶不分了
I think you'reabcconfusing nice and evil again.
让妻子欺骗丈夫 发明个处女生子abc好方便你...
Letting a woman deceive her husband byabcinventing a virgin birth just so you can--
要是孩子在圣诞那天出生会更贴切
and it obviously would have been more fittingabcif the baby had been born on christmas,
而不仅仅是在那天发明
not just invted then.
不是白血病
It's not leukemia.
癫痫 肝衰竭
Seizures,liverabcfailure--
是子痫
it's eclampsia.
这就是说不是一个救不活
This means we don'thaveabcone dead patient.
而是两个
We have two.
你患了子痫
you have a disease called eclampsia.
导致肝衰竭 肺水肿 癫痫
It causes liver failure,pulmonaryabcedema, and seizures.
也跟心肌病有关系
It's also associatedabcwith cardiomyopathy.
那是怀孕了才会得的病
That's a pregnancy disease.
她入院的时候你查过
You tested her when she came in.
可能在生产1个月内得子痫
Uh, you can get eclampsia upabcto a month after giving birth.
太荒唐了
That's ridiculous.
她怀孕了 我们怎么会都不知道?
How could she hide a pregnancy?
肥大的衣服 她本身体格就比较大
Loose clothes. She's heavy to begin with.
可能是早产
It was probably premature.
如果是3个礼拜之前abc体检的时候可能查不出来
If it was three weeks ago, they couldabchave missed it on a physical exam.
你戒酒就是因为孩子 是吧?
The baby's why youabcquit drinking,isn't it?
所以你问我我有没有孩子
Why you asked me if I had kids.
所以你才会觉得内疚
Why you feel guilty.
对不起
I'm sorry.
谁干的?
who did this to you?
Simon
Simon.
没有那么糟
It wasn't bad.
我们交往了一段时间 谁都没告诉
We were like boyfriend/ girlfriendabcfor a while, we just didn't tell anyone.
他不知道...
He doesn't evenabcknow about--
孩子怎么了?
what happened to the baby?
我本来想送去领养
I was gonna give it away.
要是学校里同学发现了...abc她要出来时 我在施食处
If they found out at school-- I was atabcthe soup kitchen and she started coming.
街那边有栋空房子 但是她却没气了
There was this empty house down theabcstreet, but then she wasn't breathing.
我尽了一切力 但是我没办法abc对... 对不起
I tried so hard,but I couldn'tabcdo anything. I'M... so sorry.
要是我在医院里生产 也许她能活下来
If I had her in a hospital,abcmaybe she'd be alive.
你能治好吗?
Can you cure this?
心脏和肝脏的损伤是永久性的
The damage to the heart andabcliver are permanent.
我会死吗?
I'm gonna die?
对不起
I'm sorry.
我甚至都没有埋葬她
I didn't even bury her.
只把外套盖在了她身上
I just put my coat over her.
滚
get out of my house.
我是一个医生
I'm a doctor.
我不管你是什么人
I don't care who you are.
你有没有 发现一个婴儿的尸体?
Diyou, uh... find the body of a baby?
我说了 滚
I said get out.
Michael?
michael?
你是谁?
Who are you?
这不是你的孩子 你太瘦了
That's not your baby. You're tiny.
你不可能3周前才生完孩子
There's no way you gaveabcbirth three weeks ago.
是我姐姐的
She's my sister's.
孩子病了 她需要干净的水 温暖的环境
That baby is sick. She needsabcclean water. She needs real heat.
她可能天生气管阻塞
She was probably born with aabcpartially blocked airway and--
甚至脑损伤
Might even have brain damage.
在这种地方你没法照顾好她
You can't take care ofabcherin a place like this.
闭嘴
shut up.
- 一直是我照顾她abc- 我知道
- I took care of her-- - I know.
是你发现的她
You found her.
你救了她的命
You saved her life.
现在你得让她离开了
Now you have to let her go.
她是谁?
Who is that?
你女儿 她活着
It's your daughter. She was alive.
有人找到了她 照顾着她
People found her and took care of her.
* 原地打转 *
* Runnin' the race like a mouseabcin a cage gettin' nowhere *abc"Whisper" By A Fine Fernzy
她真漂亮
She's beautiful.
* 但我努力了 *
* But I'm trying *
* 挣扎向前 但是作茧自缚 *
* forgin' ahead but I'mabcstuck in the bed that I made *
* 所以我躺下 *
* so I'm lying *
* 但如果你贴近我 *
* but if you keep real close *
* 贴得非常近 *
* yeah,you stay real close *
* 我会抓住你 *
* I will reach you *
* 我只剩 *
* I'm down to a whisper *
* 白日梦小山上的一口气 *
* in a day dream on a hill *
Kunter
kutner.
- 不能移植?abc- 我们申请了 病得太重
- No transplant?abc- We appealed. Too sick.
还能撑多久?
How much time does she have left?
屈指可数了
A couple of days at most.
孩子呢?
What about the baby?
看上去挺健康的 目前还没法下定论
Seems healthy, butabcit's too early to tell.
她还要留院观察几天 但之后...
She's in the hospital for observationabcfor a few days,but after that--
最好的结局abc也就是跟着未成年的父亲
best case, winds up withabcher teenage father
他最近才当选校霸
who just got voted captainabcof the varsity bullying team.
他还是个孩子
He's just a kid.
- 你还好吗?abc- 我得走了
- You all right?abc- I gotta go.
* 我放弃了平心静气的打算 *
* And I've stopped trying toabcfind any peace in my mind *
* 因为适得其反 *
* 'cause it tangles the wires *
* 但是如果你贴近我 *
* but if you keep real close *
* 贴近 *
* Yeah, you stay real close *
- Jonathanabc- 我是
- jonathan.abc- Yeah?
我是... 我是Lawrence Kutner
It--it's, uh...abcit's lawrence kutner.
你来干嘛?
Wh-why are you here?
我想道歉
I wanted to apologize.
对不起 我高中的时候那样整你
For all of the horrible stuffabcI did to you in high school.
对不起
I'm sorry.
* 只剩一口气 *
* Shut down to a whisper *
* 听得到吗? *
* can you hear me?*
* Can you hear me?*
* 一直到 *
* Still The sound *
* 余音散去 *
* tires on my lips...*
她以后怎么办?
what's gonna happen to her?
我和两边的祖父母都谈过了
I spoke to both sets of gnd parents.
太痛苦了 他们要把她送去领养
It's too painful. They'reabcputting her up for adoption.
你要怎么办?
What are you gonna do?
我已经和律师谈过了
I already spoke to a lawyer.
我要领养她
I become a fosterabcparent and then I adopt.
圣诞快乐 Cuddy
merry christmas,cuddy.
大家人呢?
Where is everybody?
在楼底下派对
Down at the party.
我听说Janice又回来了
I heard janice is back on the trial.
我送你的圣诞礼物
My christmas gift to you.
我错了 你不是House
I was wrong. You're not house.
嗯 这是我送自己的圣诞礼物
Yeah, well, th's myabcchristmas gift to myself.
我们应该去派对
We should go to the party.
对
We should.
* 火上烤着栗子 *
* chestnuts roasting on an open fire *
* 小精灵掐你的鼻子 *
* jack frost nippin'at your nose *
* 合唱团唱出 *
* yuletide carols *
* 圣诞颂歌 *
* being sung by a choir... *